<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal on Greg McMullen</title>
    <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/categories/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal on Greg McMullen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 12:00:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/categories/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Season Recap: 2012-13</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2013/05/season-recap-2012-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 12:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2013/05/season-recap-2012-13/</guid>
      <description>With my first collegiate season under my belt, I am definitely looking forward to my second year (and more, if possible).
We wrapped up the season with 20 individual records (more with diving) and had two compete at the NCAA Division III National Championships.
Challenges Being a first-year (first-time collegiate) coach was intimidating. While I felt the need to approach the athletes different, I didn&amp;#8217;t. They were responsive to my critiques and criticisms, inviting the views from a coach they didn&amp;#8217;t know that well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reaffirming a Coaching Career Choice</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2013/01/reaffirming-a-coaching-career-choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 09:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2013/01/reaffirming-a-coaching-career-choice/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I received a series of text messages from a former swimmer. I only coached this athlete for two high school seasons and not only did he have an impact on my life, but these messages clearly showed that I had an impact on his as well.
 Hey Coach Greg! I just wanted to shoot you a quick text here. I just wanted to let you know how grateful I was to have had you as my head coach senior year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working at Rose-Hulman</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/07/working-at-rose-hulman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 18:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/07/working-at-rose-hulman/</guid>
      <description>For the last three weeks, I&amp;#8217;ve been working towards finding my own way. The people at Rose-Hulman have made my transition extremely easy and incredibly fun.
I&amp;#8217;ve been introduced to a large group of people and have already been given a large project that will change the way this school looks at social media. I&amp;#8217;m looking forward to getting it off the ground.
This new position I&amp;#8217;m in has been a very large change compared to where I was previously, they are embracing technology and putting the latest and greatest tools in front of me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Working Life</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/04/my-working-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 09:37:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/04/my-working-life/</guid>
      <description>People have asked me, why do you work so much? I didn&amp;#8217;t really understand what they meant until this last year. Throughout the year, I work 3 different jobs which range, at times, from 5:30am until 8:00pm.
Why do you work so much? I don&amp;#8217;t do it for the pay, I don&amp;#8217;t do it for the recognition. I do it because I want to pay off my bills. I&amp;#8217;ve worked the same base full-time job for nearly 3 years, and honestly it&amp;#8217;s helped me pay off my debt better than I thought it would.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My 2012 Resolutions</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/01/my-2012-resolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2012 22:29:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/01/my-2012-resolutions/</guid>
      <description>I honestly can&amp;#8217;t remember the last time I actually wanted to make a New Year&amp;#8217;s resolution. However, I am wanting to better my life and others around me so here it is; making it 100% public for the first time.
First: Eat out less and stop buying microwaveable/prepackaged frozen foods.
Second: Work out more. (The typical New Year&amp;#8217;s Resolution, right?)
Third: Take care of myself and things I care about first and make more time for these things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am a failure</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/11/i-am-a-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 12:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/11/i-am-a-failure/</guid>
      <description>There are two Michael Jordan quotes that truly are amazing. Actually, he has quite a few quotes on this topic; the two I am going to focus on are some of my favorites.
 I&amp;#8217;ve missed more than 9000 shots in my career. I&amp;#8217;ve lost almost 300 games. 26 times, I&amp;#8217;ve been trusted to take the game winning shot and missed. I&amp;#8217;ve failed over and over and over again in my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Risks; Meeting Opportunity</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/taking-risks-meeting-opportunity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 21:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/taking-risks-meeting-opportunity/</guid>
      <description>Recently I was talking to an online acquaintance regarding the process of making tough decisions. My question to you is why are you afraid to take the risks that will make you happy?
People are Safe You know what will make you happy don&amp;#8217;t you? So why aren&amp;#8217;t you doing everything you can to do it? I&amp;#8217;ve seen in my life that I need encouragement do try something different. When I saw the coaching position open I was hesitant to apply, why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Law of the Lid</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/law-of-the-lid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 12:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/law-of-the-lid/</guid>
      <description>Recently I was given a copy of The 21 Irrefutable Laws of Leadership and decided that I will partake in applying these laws to my life online.
My hope is that I can also urge you, my readers and friends, to also partake and keep me accountable for my goals, dreams and ambitions as I also help you.
Major Goals List your major goals. No more than ten; no less than five.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Describe &amp;#8216;Today&amp;#8217;</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-describe-#8216today%238217/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 11:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-describe-#8216today%238217/</guid>
      <description>Today&amp;#8217;s task seems slightly more daunting than yesterday. Somehow I am supposed to describe my day in only one sentence. Shouldn&amp;#8217;t be too hard&amp;#8230;right? Author Liz Danzico.
 &amp;#8220;Your genuine action will explain itself, and will explain your other genuine actions. Your conformity explains nothing. The force of character is cumulative. – Ralph Waldo Emerson, Self-Reliance&amp;#8221;
 My Response: Don&amp;#8217;t let today get in the way of the rest of your life; you&amp;#8217;ll have struggles but keep your friends and family close, they&amp;#8217;re the best support you&amp;#8217;ll ever need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: 15 Minutes to Live</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/05/trust30-15-minutes-to-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2011 19:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/05/trust30-15-minutes-to-live/</guid>
      <description>In an effort to improve my writing skills and to post more frequently I have decided to join the #Trust30 effort. Luckily I won&amp;#8217;t have to be too creative as there will be prompts for me to write about. Today&amp;#8217;s prompt by Gwen Bell is &amp;#8220;15 Minutes to Live&amp;#8221;
 &amp;#8220;We are afraid of truth, afraid of fortune, afraid of death, and afraid of each other. Our age yields no great and perfect persons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>