<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>personal life on Greg McMullen</title>
    <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/personal-life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in personal life on Greg McMullen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 18:00:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/personal-life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Working at Rose-Hulman</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/07/working-at-rose-hulman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 18:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/07/working-at-rose-hulman/</guid>
      <description>For the last three weeks, I&amp;#8217;ve been working towards finding my own way. The people at Rose-Hulman have made my transition extremely easy and incredibly fun.
I&amp;#8217;ve been introduced to a large group of people and have already been given a large project that will change the way this school looks at social media. I&amp;#8217;m looking forward to getting it off the ground.
This new position I&amp;#8217;m in has been a very large change compared to where I was previously, they are embracing technology and putting the latest and greatest tools in front of me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Handle Disappointment?</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/07/do-you-handle-disappointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 11:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/07/do-you-handle-disappointment/</guid>
      <description>Success is Peace of Mind which is a direct result of self satisfaction in knowing you made the effort to do the best of which you are capable. - John Wooden
 If you were one of the many Americans watching the Women&amp;#8217;s National team make a run toward the FIFA Women&amp;#8217;s World Cup Final were you disappointed?
By looking at the team accomplishments, you&amp;#8217;ll proud!
Team USA Accomplishments  Hope Solo went 1,054 minutes without allowing a goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Divine Idea</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-divine-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 12:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-divine-idea/</guid>
      <description>Imitation is Suicide. Insist on yourself; never imitate. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 Write down in which areas of your life you have to overcome these suicidal tendencies of imitation, and how you can transform them into a newborn you – one that doesn’t hide its uniqueness, but thrives on it. There is a &amp;#8220;divine idea which each of us represents&amp;#8221; – which is yours?
Every day I fight with the owner of my organization about trying something new within the realm of marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Top 10 Fears</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-top-10-fears/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2011 22:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-top-10-fears/</guid>
      <description>The other terror that scares us from self-trust is our consistency; a reverence for our past act or word, because the eyes of others have no other data for computing our orbit than our past acts, and we are loath to disappoint them. &amp;#8211; Ralph Waldo Emerson
Emerson says: “Always do what you are afraid to do.” What is ‘too scary’ to write about? Try doing it now.
So I wasn&amp;#8217;t really sure about what to write on this prompt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Help Change Stalking Laws</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/help-change-stalking-laws/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 14:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/help-change-stalking-laws/</guid>
      <description>How You Can Help
On June 23, Jodi’s Voice will be having an event in Las Vegas called Fight Stalking in partnership with Sky Combat Ace. Celebrities from the world of entertainment will be going up against each other in aerial combat. Supporters of each celebrity can back their champions with donations and messages of support, and the funds raised will go to Jodi’s Voice.
And it’s the June event for Danny Brown’s 12for12K, an organization that aims to raise a minimum of $12,000 for a different charity each month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: 5 Years, Before and After</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-5-years-before-and-after/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 09:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-5-years-before-and-after/</guid>
      <description>There will be an agreement in whatever variety of actions, so they be each honest and natural in their hour. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 What would you say to the person you were five years ago? What will you say to the person you’ll be in five years?
Five years ago, I was in transition between the University of Evansville and Xavier University. The year was disappointing to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: How Bold Will You Be?</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-how-bold-will-you-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2011 08:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-how-bold-will-you-be/</guid>
      <description>Our arts, our occupations, our marriages, our religion, we have not chosen, but society has chosen for us. We are parlour soldiers. We shun the rugged battle of fate, where strength is born. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 Next to Resistance, rational thought is the artist or entrepreneurs worst enemy. Bad things happen when we employ rational thought, because rational thought comes from the ego. Instead, we want to work from the Self, that is, from instinct and intuition, from the unconscious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Come Alive!</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-come-alive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2011 00:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-come-alive/</guid>
      <description>Life wastes itself while we are preparing to live. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 If you had one week left to live, would you still be doing what you’re doing now? In what areas of your life are you preparing to live? Take them off your To Do list and add them to a To Stop list. Resolve to only do what makes you come alive.
Bonus: How can your goals improve the present and not keep you in a perpetual “always something better” spiral?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: My Personal (un)Shared Belief</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-my-personal-unshared-belief/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 19:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-my-personal-unshared-belief/</guid>
      <description>It is easy in the world to live after the world’s opinion; it is easy in solitude to live after our own; but the great man is he who in the midst of the crowd keeps with perfect sweetness the independence of solitude. &amp;#8211; Ralph Waldo Emerson, Self-Reliance
 The world is powered by passionate people, powerful ideas, and fearless action. What’s one strong belief you possess that isn’t shared by your closest friends or family?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Preparing for Work Life</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/09/preparing-for-work-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2010 09:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/09/preparing-for-work-life/</guid>
      <description>While you are in school, no one really tells you how to prepare for work life. Honestly, I wasn&amp;#8217;t sure I could make it in the real world. However, I&amp;#8217;m currently working a full time job, paid off 2 student loans (2 to go), picked up my cell phone bill and bought a car! The best part is that I&amp;#8217;m only 23 years old.
No one can prepare you for the real world better than yourself!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>