<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>chasing your dreams on Greg McMullen</title>
    <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/chasing-your-dreams/</link>
    <description>Recent content in chasing your dreams on Greg McMullen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2011 13:41:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/chasing-your-dreams/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What Makes you Better?</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/07/what-makes-you-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2011 13:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/07/what-makes-you-better/</guid>
      <description>I was recently interviewed for a head coach job at a swim club. I surprised myself when I was asked the question.
 What makes you different/better than the next person that we bring in?
 My response, &amp;#8220;Nothing.&amp;#8221;
What the @#$^% are you thinking? How am I supposed to know what makes me different from people I&amp;#8217;ve never met? For all I know they could be 30 years old and have coached for 15 years, am I better than them?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Searching: What Not to Do!</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/job-searching-what-not-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2011 19:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/job-searching-what-not-to-do/</guid>
      <description>Job searching is a necessary part of your professional life. However, there are some do&amp;#8217;s and don&amp;#8217;ts. Right now I&amp;#8217;m going to talk about something that hits very close to home when it comes to searching for your next job or even your dream career.
While the title of this post hints at what not to do I also want to touch on a few things that you should do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Divine Idea</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-divine-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 12:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-divine-idea/</guid>
      <description>Imitation is Suicide. Insist on yourself; never imitate. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 Write down in which areas of your life you have to overcome these suicidal tendencies of imitation, and how you can transform them into a newborn you – one that doesn’t hide its uniqueness, but thrives on it. There is a &amp;#8220;divine idea which each of us represents&amp;#8221; – which is yours?
Every day I fight with the owner of my organization about trying something new within the realm of marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Top 10 Fears</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-top-10-fears/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2011 22:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-top-10-fears/</guid>
      <description>The other terror that scares us from self-trust is our consistency; a reverence for our past act or word, because the eyes of others have no other data for computing our orbit than our past acts, and we are loath to disappoint them. &amp;#8211; Ralph Waldo Emerson
Emerson says: “Always do what you are afraid to do.” What is ‘too scary’ to write about? Try doing it now.
So I wasn&amp;#8217;t really sure about what to write on this prompt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: 5 Years, Before and After</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-5-years-before-and-after/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 09:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-5-years-before-and-after/</guid>
      <description>There will be an agreement in whatever variety of actions, so they be each honest and natural in their hour. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 What would you say to the person you were five years ago? What will you say to the person you’ll be in five years?
Five years ago, I was in transition between the University of Evansville and Xavier University. The year was disappointing to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Come Alive!</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-come-alive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2011 00:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-come-alive/</guid>
      <description>Life wastes itself while we are preparing to live. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 If you had one week left to live, would you still be doing what you’re doing now? In what areas of your life are you preparing to live? Take them off your To Do list and add them to a To Stop list. Resolve to only do what makes you come alive.
Bonus: How can your goals improve the present and not keep you in a perpetual “always something better” spiral?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chasing Your Dream Job</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/08/chasing-your-dream-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2010 23:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/08/chasing-your-dream-job/</guid>
      <description>This weekend I decided to head down to visit my girlfriend, who is attending IU Medical School, and while we know that living an hour apart is going to be tough we never realized how hard it was until today around 2:00.
She and I have been together for the last five years and honestly we&amp;#8217;ve both been rather selfish with doing what we want instead of really thinking about one another.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>