<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>indiana on Greg McMullen</title>
    <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/indiana/</link>
    <description>Recent content in indiana on Greg McMullen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2011 08:59:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/indiana/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Water Under the Pier</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/water-under-the-pier/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2011 08:59:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/water-under-the-pier/</guid>
      <description>This image was captured while on vacation at Ft Myers Beach. Sarah and I were walking along the beach to this pier on our second to last morning and I decided to capture this as a Hand-Held HDR photo. All things considered, I really like the way it turned out. Not sure how I was able to capture the waves, but I&amp;#8217;m glad that I did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Personal Message</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-personal-message/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 20:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-personal-message/</guid>
      <description>To believe your own thought, to believe that what is true for you in your private heart is true for all men, that is genius. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 What is burning deep inside of you? If you could spread your personal message RIGHT NOW to 1 million people, what would you say?
If I had the chance to share my personal message with anyone, it would always be the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Top 10 Fears</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-top-10-fears/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2011 22:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-top-10-fears/</guid>
      <description>The other terror that scares us from self-trust is our consistency; a reverence for our past act or word, because the eyes of others have no other data for computing our orbit than our past acts, and we are loath to disappoint them. &amp;#8211; Ralph Waldo Emerson
Emerson says: “Always do what you are afraid to do.” What is ‘too scary’ to write about? Try doing it now.
So I wasn&amp;#8217;t really sure about what to write on this prompt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: My Personal (un)Shared Belief</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-my-personal-unshared-belief/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 19:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-my-personal-unshared-belief/</guid>
      <description>It is easy in the world to live after the world’s opinion; it is easy in solitude to live after our own; but the great man is he who in the midst of the crowd keeps with perfect sweetness the independence of solitude. &amp;#8211; Ralph Waldo Emerson, Self-Reliance
 The world is powered by passionate people, powerful ideas, and fearless action. What’s one strong belief you possess that isn’t shared by your closest friends or family?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Describe &amp;#8216;Today&amp;#8217;</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-describe-#8216today%238217/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 11:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-describe-#8216today%238217/</guid>
      <description>Today&amp;#8217;s task seems slightly more daunting than yesterday. Somehow I am supposed to describe my day in only one sentence. Shouldn&amp;#8217;t be too hard&amp;#8230;right? Author Liz Danzico.
 &amp;#8220;Your genuine action will explain itself, and will explain your other genuine actions. Your conformity explains nothing. The force of character is cumulative. – Ralph Waldo Emerson, Self-Reliance&amp;#8221;
 My Response: Don&amp;#8217;t let today get in the way of the rest of your life; you&amp;#8217;ll have struggles but keep your friends and family close, they&amp;#8217;re the best support you&amp;#8217;ll ever need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indy Zoo and Garden</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/05/indy-zoo-and-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2011 22:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/05/indy-zoo-and-garden/</guid>
      <description>Decided to take a trip up to the Indy Zoo. Sarah and I really enjoyed being outside and I was surprised how active all of the animals were.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sports and Education</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/01/sports-and-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 11:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/01/sports-and-education/</guid>
      <description>Now, to start things off I&amp;#8217;m a little upset and frustrated at this quote from Cam Newton after the Auburn Tigers beat the Oregon Ducks in the BCS Title game. So if this seems a little off topic, I want to apologize.
 &amp;#8220;I don&amp;#8217;t want nobody to feel sorry for me, because throughout this year didn&amp;#8217;t nobody feel sorry for Auburn,&amp;#8221; Newton said, setting a BCS record for double negatives in a single sentence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Fall Landscapes</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/10/some-fall-landscapes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2010 19:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/10/some-fall-landscapes/</guid>
      <description>Decided to go to the Northwest Park Annex and take some pictures. Let me know what you think!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>