<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketing on Greg McMullen</title>
    <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/categories/marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketing on Greg McMullen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 12:27:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/categories/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving Your Team Through Cuts</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/11/improving-your-team-through-cuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2010 12:27:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/11/improving-your-team-through-cuts/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m starting to find myself in some tough spots. Last week we had a few guys that were having a rough time even making it through pushing off of a wall without stopping immediately. This combined with the fact that we have a 6-lane pool with over 30 swimmers meant that we unfortunately had to make some cuts.
Now for a business example. We (at @UniqueHomeSol) recently setup a marketing group to head up our online, TV and print campaigns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You Happy?</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/09/are-you-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2010 10:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/09/are-you-happy/</guid>
      <description>Author: Randy Clark
Recently, over lunch, Greg asked if I would guest post about separating work and Life. As I considered what I would like to share, I realized how many different approaches were available on this subject. Do I talk of social media and how difficult it is to separate work from social media 24&amp;frasl;7? How about strategies to balance your life? How to make work fun or eliminate stress?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding your First Job</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/09/finding-your-first-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2010 15:46:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/09/finding-your-first-job/</guid>
      <description>I know that when I started looking for jobs in college I looked for just about any place that was offering a job. The worst part about it was looking for something within my Degree (BSBA in Business Management). Obviously trying to find a &amp;#8220;management&amp;#8221; job was out of the question unless it would be lower-level.
Target your Ideal Job The best advice that I can even begin to give to Juniors and Seniors looking for a permanent job is to target the type of job that you want not just what you pre-qualify yourself for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Importance of your Avatar</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/08/importance-of-your-avatar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 10:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/08/importance-of-your-avatar/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m sure that you&amp;#8217;ve heard the old phrase &amp;#8220;Don&amp;#8217;t Judge a book by it&amp;#8217;s cover&amp;#8221; but is that really how we operate? I know that I am guilty of judging someone based on their looks.
When we are looking for something or someone we look at links, videos, and images. What I want to talk about is your personal appearance, particularly in your online avatar. If you were to show up to an interview in a pair of ripped jeans, a dirty polo and basketball shoes would you be received the same as if you were to show up wearing a professionally cleaned and tailored suit?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>