<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on Greg McMullen</title>
    <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on Greg McMullen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 09:29:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: 5 Years, Before and After</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-5-years-before-and-after/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 09:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-5-years-before-and-after/</guid>
      <description>There will be an agreement in whatever variety of actions, so they be each honest and natural in their hour. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 What would you say to the person you were five years ago? What will you say to the person you’ll be in five years?
Five years ago, I was in transition between the University of Evansville and Xavier University. The year was disappointing to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: How Bold Will You Be?</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-how-bold-will-you-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2011 08:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-how-bold-will-you-be/</guid>
      <description>Our arts, our occupations, our marriages, our religion, we have not chosen, but society has chosen for us. We are parlour soldiers. We shun the rugged battle of fate, where strength is born. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 Next to Resistance, rational thought is the artist or entrepreneurs worst enemy. Bad things happen when we employ rational thought, because rational thought comes from the ego. Instead, we want to work from the Self, that is, from instinct and intuition, from the unconscious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Travel</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2011 12:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-travel/</guid>
      <description>If we live truly, we shall see truly. &amp;#8211; Ralph Waldo Emerson
 Not everyone wants to travel the world, but most people can identify at least one place in the world they’d like to visit before they die. Where is that place for you, and what will you do to make sure you get there?
I&amp;#8217;ve been lucky&amp;#8230; While I was still in school I was able to travel to the one place outside of the US that I&amp;#8217;ve always wanted to visit, the Republic of Ireland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Describe &amp;#8216;Today&amp;#8217;</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-describe-#8216today%238217/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 11:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-describe-#8216today%238217/</guid>
      <description>Today&amp;#8217;s task seems slightly more daunting than yesterday. Somehow I am supposed to describe my day in only one sentence. Shouldn&amp;#8217;t be too hard&amp;#8230;right? Author Liz Danzico.
 &amp;#8220;Your genuine action will explain itself, and will explain your other genuine actions. Your conformity explains nothing. The force of character is cumulative. – Ralph Waldo Emerson, Self-Reliance&amp;#8221;
 My Response: Don&amp;#8217;t let today get in the way of the rest of your life; you&amp;#8217;ll have struggles but keep your friends and family close, they&amp;#8217;re the best support you&amp;#8217;ll ever need.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>