<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on Greg McMullen</title>
    <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/categories/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on Greg McMullen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 09:35:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://gregoryamcmullen.com/categories/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reaffirming a Coaching Career Choice</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2013/01/reaffirming-a-coaching-career-choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 09:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2013/01/reaffirming-a-coaching-career-choice/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I received a series of text messages from a former swimmer. I only coached this athlete for two high school seasons and not only did he have an impact on my life, but these messages clearly showed that I had an impact on his as well.
 Hey Coach Greg! I just wanted to shoot you a quick text here. I just wanted to let you know how grateful I was to have had you as my head coach senior year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working at Rose-Hulman</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/07/working-at-rose-hulman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2012 18:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/07/working-at-rose-hulman/</guid>
      <description>For the last three weeks, I&amp;#8217;ve been working towards finding my own way. The people at Rose-Hulman have made my transition extremely easy and incredibly fun.
I&amp;#8217;ve been introduced to a large group of people and have already been given a large project that will change the way this school looks at social media. I&amp;#8217;m looking forward to getting it off the ground.
This new position I&amp;#8217;m in has been a very large change compared to where I was previously, they are embracing technology and putting the latest and greatest tools in front of me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2011-2012 Season Recap</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/03/2011-2012-season-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 09:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/03/2011-2012-season-recap/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s simple, Coaches and athletes have to have goals. However, you have to make sure that the athletes and coaching staff buy into those goals and are all on the same page too. How do you do that? How does it work? What does it look like before/during/after? Well, this season was all about that.
This season was a different monster; it was something I wasn&amp;#8217;t quite ready for. I was responsible for practice development, discipline and general team maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My 2012 Resolutions</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/01/my-2012-resolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2012 22:29:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/01/my-2012-resolutions/</guid>
      <description>I honestly can&amp;#8217;t remember the last time I actually wanted to make a New Year&amp;#8217;s resolution. However, I am wanting to better my life and others around me so here it is; making it 100% public for the first time.
First: Eat out less and stop buying microwaveable/prepackaged frozen foods.
Second: Work out more. (The typical New Year&amp;#8217;s Resolution, right?)
Third: Take care of myself and things I care about first and make more time for these things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am a failure</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/11/i-am-a-failure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2011 12:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/11/i-am-a-failure/</guid>
      <description>There are two Michael Jordan quotes that truly are amazing. Actually, he has quite a few quotes on this topic; the two I am going to focus on are some of my favorites.
 I&amp;#8217;ve missed more than 9000 shots in my career. I&amp;#8217;ve lost almost 300 games. 26 times, I&amp;#8217;ve been trusted to take the game winning shot and missed. I&amp;#8217;ve failed over and over and over again in my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Risks; Meeting Opportunity</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/taking-risks-meeting-opportunity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 21:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/taking-risks-meeting-opportunity/</guid>
      <description>Recently I was talking to an online acquaintance regarding the process of making tough decisions. My question to you is why are you afraid to take the risks that will make you happy?
People are Safe You know what will make you happy don&amp;#8217;t you? So why aren&amp;#8217;t you doing everything you can to do it? I&amp;#8217;ve seen in my life that I need encouragement do try something different. When I saw the coaching position open I was hesitant to apply, why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Law of the Lid</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/law-of-the-lid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 12:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/law-of-the-lid/</guid>
      <description>Recently I was given a copy of The 21 Irrefutable Laws of Leadership and decided that I will partake in applying these laws to my life online.
My hope is that I can also urge you, my readers and friends, to also partake and keep me accountable for my goals, dreams and ambitions as I also help you.
Major Goals List your major goals. No more than ten; no less than five.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Workout Ideas</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/simple-workout-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 08:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/simple-workout-ideas/</guid>
      <description>Everyone&amp;#8217;s busy. How do you manage to get a workout in? Do you have an expensive gym membership? Do you just walk or run around your neighborhood? Or do you have trouble finding the motivation to do a workout?
Today, I&amp;#8217;m going to give you just a few simple workout ideas using nothing but a resistance band, AKA Stretch Cords.
Resistance bands come in different lengths and resistance levels. The nice thing about using resistance bands is that you don&amp;#8217;t have to worry about dropping something heavy on your foot, so this makes for a nice workout even when you are alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Handle Disappointment?</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/07/do-you-handle-disappointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 11:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/07/do-you-handle-disappointment/</guid>
      <description>Success is Peace of Mind which is a direct result of self satisfaction in knowing you made the effort to do the best of which you are capable. - John Wooden
 If you were one of the many Americans watching the Women&amp;#8217;s National team make a run toward the FIFA Women&amp;#8217;s World Cup Final were you disappointed?
By looking at the team accomplishments, you&amp;#8217;ll proud!
Team USA Accomplishments  Hope Solo went 1,054 minutes without allowing a goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Searching: What Not to Do!</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/job-searching-what-not-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2011 19:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/job-searching-what-not-to-do/</guid>
      <description>Job searching is a necessary part of your professional life. However, there are some do&amp;#8217;s and don&amp;#8217;ts. Right now I&amp;#8217;m going to talk about something that hits very close to home when it comes to searching for your next job or even your dream career.
While the title of this post hints at what not to do I also want to touch on a few things that you should do.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>