<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal on Greg McMullen</title>
    <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal on Greg McMullen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2011 19:37:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Searching: What Not to Do!</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/job-searching-what-not-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2011 19:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/job-searching-what-not-to-do/</guid>
      <description>Job searching is a necessary part of your professional life. However, there are some do&amp;#8217;s and don&amp;#8217;ts. Right now I&amp;#8217;m going to talk about something that hits very close to home when it comes to searching for your next job or even your dream career.
While the title of this post hints at what not to do I also want to touch on a few things that you should do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Personal Message</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-personal-message/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 20:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-personal-message/</guid>
      <description>To believe your own thought, to believe that what is true for you in your private heart is true for all men, that is genius. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 What is burning deep inside of you? If you could spread your personal message RIGHT NOW to 1 million people, what would you say?
If I had the chance to share my personal message with anyone, it would always be the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Travel</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2011 12:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-travel/</guid>
      <description>If we live truly, we shall see truly. &amp;#8211; Ralph Waldo Emerson
 Not everyone wants to travel the world, but most people can identify at least one place in the world they’d like to visit before they die. Where is that place for you, and what will you do to make sure you get there?
I&amp;#8217;ve been lucky&amp;#8230; While I was still in school I was able to travel to the one place outside of the US that I&amp;#8217;ve always wanted to visit, the Republic of Ireland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Describe &amp;#8216;Today&amp;#8217;</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-describe-#8216today%238217/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 11:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-describe-#8216today%238217/</guid>
      <description>Today&amp;#8217;s task seems slightly more daunting than yesterday. Somehow I am supposed to describe my day in only one sentence. Shouldn&amp;#8217;t be too hard&amp;#8230;right? Author Liz Danzico.
 &amp;#8220;Your genuine action will explain itself, and will explain your other genuine actions. Your conformity explains nothing. The force of character is cumulative. – Ralph Waldo Emerson, Self-Reliance&amp;#8221;
 My Response: Don&amp;#8217;t let today get in the way of the rest of your life; you&amp;#8217;ll have struggles but keep your friends and family close, they&amp;#8217;re the best support you&amp;#8217;ll ever need.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>