<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trust30 on Greg McMullen</title>
    <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/categories/trust30/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trust30 on Greg McMullen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2011 13:04:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/categories/trust30/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Courage to Connect</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-courage-to-connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2011 13:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-courage-to-connect/</guid>
      <description>Men imagine that they communicate their virtue or vice only by overt actions, and do not see that virtue or vice emit a breath every moment. &amp;#8211; Ralph Waldo Emerson
 Who is one person that you’ve been dying to connect with, but just haven’t had the courage to reach out to? First, reflect on why you want to get in touch with them. Then, reach out and set up a meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Surprise!</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2011 12:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-surprise/</guid>
      <description>I will not hide my tastes or aversions. I will so trust that what is deep is holy, if we follow the truth, it will bring us out safe at last. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 Think of a time when you didn’t think you were capable of doing something, but then surprised yourself. How will you surprise yourself this week?
You want to know something about me? I don&amp;#8217;t run, ever!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Divine Idea</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-divine-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 12:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-divine-idea/</guid>
      <description>Imitation is Suicide. Insist on yourself; never imitate. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 Write down in which areas of your life you have to overcome these suicidal tendencies of imitation, and how you can transform them into a newborn you – one that doesn’t hide its uniqueness, but thrives on it. There is a &amp;#8220;divine idea which each of us represents&amp;#8221; – which is yours?
Every day I fight with the owner of my organization about trying something new within the realm of marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Personal Message</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-personal-message/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 20:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-personal-message/</guid>
      <description>To believe your own thought, to believe that what is true for you in your private heart is true for all men, that is genius. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 What is burning deep inside of you? If you could spread your personal message RIGHT NOW to 1 million people, what would you say?
If I had the chance to share my personal message with anyone, it would always be the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Top 10 Fears</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-top-10-fears/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2011 22:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-top-10-fears/</guid>
      <description>The other terror that scares us from self-trust is our consistency; a reverence for our past act or word, because the eyes of others have no other data for computing our orbit than our past acts, and we are loath to disappoint them. &amp;#8211; Ralph Waldo Emerson
Emerson says: “Always do what you are afraid to do.” What is ‘too scary’ to write about? Try doing it now.
So I wasn&amp;#8217;t really sure about what to write on this prompt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: 5 Years, Before and After</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-5-years-before-and-after/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2011 09:29:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-5-years-before-and-after/</guid>
      <description>There will be an agreement in whatever variety of actions, so they be each honest and natural in their hour. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 What would you say to the person you were five years ago? What will you say to the person you’ll be in five years?
Five years ago, I was in transition between the University of Evansville and Xavier University. The year was disappointing to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: How Bold Will You Be?</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-how-bold-will-you-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2011 08:13:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-how-bold-will-you-be/</guid>
      <description>Our arts, our occupations, our marriages, our religion, we have not chosen, but society has chosen for us. We are parlour soldiers. We shun the rugged battle of fate, where strength is born. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 Next to Resistance, rational thought is the artist or entrepreneurs worst enemy. Bad things happen when we employ rational thought, because rational thought comes from the ego. Instead, we want to work from the Self, that is, from instinct and intuition, from the unconscious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Come Alive!</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-come-alive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2011 00:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-come-alive/</guid>
      <description>Life wastes itself while we are preparing to live. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 If you had one week left to live, would you still be doing what you’re doing now? In what areas of your life are you preparing to live? Take them off your To Do list and add them to a To Stop list. Resolve to only do what makes you come alive.
Bonus: How can your goals improve the present and not keep you in a perpetual “always something better” spiral?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Travel</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2011 12:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-travel/</guid>
      <description>If we live truly, we shall see truly. &amp;#8211; Ralph Waldo Emerson
 Not everyone wants to travel the world, but most people can identify at least one place in the world they’d like to visit before they die. Where is that place for you, and what will you do to make sure you get there?
I&amp;#8217;ve been lucky&amp;#8230; While I was still in school I was able to travel to the one place outside of the US that I&amp;#8217;ve always wanted to visit, the Republic of Ireland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Post-It and Wait</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-post-it-and-wait/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2011 11:22:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-post-it-and-wait/</guid>
      <description>That which each can do best, none but his Maker can teach him. Where is the master who could have taught Shakespeare? Where is the master who could have instructed Franklin, or Washington, or Bacon, or Newton? &amp;hellip; Shakespeare will never be made by the study of Shakespeare. Do that which is assigned you, and you cannot hope too much or dare too much. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 Identify one of your biggest challenges at the moment (ie I don’t feel passionate about my work) and turn it into a question (ie How can I do work I’m passionate about?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>