<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>health on Greg McMullen</title>
    <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/health/</link>
    <description>Recent content in health on Greg McMullen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 May 2012 22:22:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Coaches and Our Health</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/05/coaches-and-our-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2012 22:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/05/coaches-and-our-health/</guid>
      <description>The other day, I finally decided to weigh myself. I weighed in at 194.4lbs. New goal, weigh in the 180&amp;#8217;s before August 11.
The immediate question on my mind is not, &amp;#8220;why don&amp;#8217;t I take better care of myself.&amp;#8221; Rather it&amp;#8217;s &amp;#8220;why is it coaches seem to take better care of their athletes than themselves.&amp;#8221; Maybe I&amp;#8217;m wrong, but I would love for others to chime in.
So I want to reach out to all gathering ideas on the subject and how we can change our actions to better portray the things we teach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Law of the Lid</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/law-of-the-lid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 12:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/law-of-the-lid/</guid>
      <description>Recently I was given a copy of The 21 Irrefutable Laws of Leadership and decided that I will partake in applying these laws to my life online.
My hope is that I can also urge you, my readers and friends, to also partake and keep me accountable for my goals, dreams and ambitions as I also help you.
Major Goals List your major goals. No more than ten; no less than five.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Workout Ideas</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/simple-workout-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 08:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/simple-workout-ideas/</guid>
      <description>Everyone&amp;#8217;s busy. How do you manage to get a workout in? Do you have an expensive gym membership? Do you just walk or run around your neighborhood? Or do you have trouble finding the motivation to do a workout?
Today, I&amp;#8217;m going to give you just a few simple workout ideas using nothing but a resistance band, AKA Stretch Cords.
Resistance bands come in different lengths and resistance levels. The nice thing about using resistance bands is that you don&amp;#8217;t have to worry about dropping something heavy on your foot, so this makes for a nice workout even when you are alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthier Living</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/03/healthier-living/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 10:49:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/03/healthier-living/</guid>
      <description>So as I&amp;#8217;m progressing through my 20s I&amp;#8217;ve realized that I&amp;#8217;m no where near where I need to be in regards to my health. It&amp;#8217;s always a shock as to how I&amp;#8217;ve been able to get these last 4 to 5 years without realizing what I need to do sooner.
I&amp;#8217;m writing this post as a reminder to myself and to also have others help me stay accountable for my workouts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>