<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Greg McMullen</title>
    <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/greg-mcmullen/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Greg McMullen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 21:51:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/greg-mcmullen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Risks; Meeting Opportunity</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/taking-risks-meeting-opportunity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 21:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/taking-risks-meeting-opportunity/</guid>
      <description>Recently I was talking to an online acquaintance regarding the process of making tough decisions. My question to you is why are you afraid to take the risks that will make you happy?
People are Safe You know what will make you happy don&amp;#8217;t you? So why aren&amp;#8217;t you doing everything you can to do it? I&amp;#8217;ve seen in my life that I need encouragement do try something different. When I saw the coaching position open I was hesitant to apply, why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Water Under the Pier</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/water-under-the-pier/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2011 08:59:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/water-under-the-pier/</guid>
      <description>This image was captured while on vacation at Ft Myers Beach. Sarah and I were walking along the beach to this pier on our second to last morning and I decided to capture this as a Hand-Held HDR photo. All things considered, I really like the way it turned out. Not sure how I was able to capture the waves, but I&amp;#8217;m glad that I did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding Life&#39;s Silver Lining</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/finding-lifes-silver-lining/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 21:34:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/finding-lifes-silver-lining/</guid>
      <description>I did something out of the ordinary the other day. I saw something that caught my eye (and had my camera) and decided to stop on the side of the road and snap a photo.
It&amp;#8217;s a reminder to all of us to stop and take in the moments of our lives and find the best out of any situation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Determining your Motivation Style</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/07/determining-your-motivation-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 08:54:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/07/determining-your-motivation-style/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;#8217;ve ever watched a college basketball game, the coaching staff in the locker room is trying to &amp;#8220;psych&amp;#8221; up the team. Sometimes it works; however, it also creates undue stress in what could be your top performers.
Motivation isn&amp;#8217;t taught. It&amp;#8217;s also something that a coach or parent isn&amp;#8217;t in control of. Allowing an athlete the ability to stay relaxed in a familiar environment is more motivating than anything a coach or parent can say.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Handle Disappointment?</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/07/do-you-handle-disappointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 11:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/07/do-you-handle-disappointment/</guid>
      <description>Success is Peace of Mind which is a direct result of self satisfaction in knowing you made the effort to do the best of which you are capable. - John Wooden
 If you were one of the many Americans watching the Women&amp;#8217;s National team make a run toward the FIFA Women&amp;#8217;s World Cup Final were you disappointed?
By looking at the team accomplishments, you&amp;#8217;ll proud!
Team USA Accomplishments  Hope Solo went 1,054 minutes without allowing a goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Makes you Better?</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/07/what-makes-you-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2011 13:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/07/what-makes-you-better/</guid>
      <description>I was recently interviewed for a head coach job at a swim club. I surprised myself when I was asked the question.
 What makes you different/better than the next person that we bring in?
 My response, &amp;#8220;Nothing.&amp;#8221;
What the @#$^% are you thinking? How am I supposed to know what makes me different from people I&amp;#8217;ve never met? For all I know they could be 30 years old and have coached for 15 years, am I better than them?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Courage to Connect</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-courage-to-connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2011 13:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-courage-to-connect/</guid>
      <description>Men imagine that they communicate their virtue or vice only by overt actions, and do not see that virtue or vice emit a breath every moment. &amp;#8211; Ralph Waldo Emerson
 Who is one person that you’ve been dying to connect with, but just haven’t had the courage to reach out to? First, reflect on why you want to get in touch with them. Then, reach out and set up a meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Searching: What Not to Do!</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/job-searching-what-not-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2011 19:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/job-searching-what-not-to-do/</guid>
      <description>Job searching is a necessary part of your professional life. However, there are some do&amp;#8217;s and don&amp;#8217;ts. Right now I&amp;#8217;m going to talk about something that hits very close to home when it comes to searching for your next job or even your dream career.
While the title of this post hints at what not to do I also want to touch on a few things that you should do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Divine Idea</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-divine-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 12:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-divine-idea/</guid>
      <description>Imitation is Suicide. Insist on yourself; never imitate. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 Write down in which areas of your life you have to overcome these suicidal tendencies of imitation, and how you can transform them into a newborn you – one that doesn’t hide its uniqueness, but thrives on it. There is a &amp;#8220;divine idea which each of us represents&amp;#8221; – which is yours?
Every day I fight with the owner of my organization about trying something new within the realm of marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Personal Message</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-personal-message/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2011 20:53:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-personal-message/</guid>
      <description>To believe your own thought, to believe that what is true for you in your private heart is true for all men, that is genius. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 What is burning deep inside of you? If you could spread your personal message RIGHT NOW to 1 million people, what would you say?
If I had the chance to share my personal message with anyone, it would always be the same.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>