<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Umbraco on Greg McMullen</title>
    <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/umbraco/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Umbraco on Greg McMullen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 16:09:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/umbraco/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Umbraco Package: Form Wrangler</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2014/05/umbraco-package-form-wrangler/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 16:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2014/05/umbraco-package-form-wrangler/</guid>
      <description>Form Wrangler is a package for Umbraco that assembles a list of files, with links, from a selected media library folder ID. This package was initially designed for the Rose-Hulman Institute of Technology Website and released to the Our Umbraco community on 22 November 2013.
Form Wrangler Parameters:  Name: Media Folder Alias: mediaFolder Type: mediaCurrent  Form Wrangler CSHTML  Disclaimer: Form Wrangler was designed &amp;#8220;as-is&amp;#8221;. Greg McMullen does not provide any warranty of the item whatsoever, whether express, implied or statutory, including, but not limited to, any warranty of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose or any warranty that the contents of the item will be error-free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updated: Umbraco Page Titles</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2013/05/updated-umbraco-page-titles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2013 10:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2013/05/updated-umbraco-page-titles/</guid>
      <description>Since creating the first rendition of the Structured Page Titles for Umbraco, I decided it would be worthwhile to revisit and clean up the size of the file and make it much more readable. Umbraco makes it easy to define page titles, but this script helps reduce the repetitive nature of titles in larger sites.
To use this code you will need to create a shortPageTitle and pageTitle in your document type(s).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Structured Umbraco Page Titles</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2013/01/structured-umbraco-page-titles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 09:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2013/01/structured-umbraco-page-titles/</guid>
      <description>If you are looking for some code to generate tiered page titles within Umbraco here is an example that worked for our site. This code assumes you are using pageTitle as a DocType element.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>