<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>work and personal life on Greg McMullen</title>
    <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/work-and-personal-life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in work and personal life on Greg McMullen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 12:06:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/work-and-personal-life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Divine Idea</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-divine-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2011 12:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-divine-idea/</guid>
      <description>Imitation is Suicide. Insist on yourself; never imitate. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 Write down in which areas of your life you have to overcome these suicidal tendencies of imitation, and how you can transform them into a newborn you – one that doesn’t hide its uniqueness, but thrives on it. There is a &amp;#8220;divine idea which each of us represents&amp;#8221; – which is yours?
Every day I fight with the owner of my organization about trying something new within the realm of marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Come Alive!</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-come-alive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2011 00:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-come-alive/</guid>
      <description>Life wastes itself while we are preparing to live. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 If you had one week left to live, would you still be doing what you’re doing now? In what areas of your life are you preparing to live? Take them off your To Do list and add them to a To Stop list. Resolve to only do what makes you come alive.
Bonus: How can your goals improve the present and not keep you in a perpetual “always something better” spiral?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: My Personal (un)Shared Belief</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-my-personal-unshared-belief/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 19:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-my-personal-unshared-belief/</guid>
      <description>It is easy in the world to live after the world’s opinion; it is easy in solitude to live after our own; but the great man is he who in the midst of the crowd keeps with perfect sweetness the independence of solitude. &amp;#8211; Ralph Waldo Emerson, Self-Reliance
 The world is powered by passionate people, powerful ideas, and fearless action. What’s one strong belief you possess that isn’t shared by your closest friends or family?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Describe &amp;#8216;Today&amp;#8217;</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-describe-#8216today%238217/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 11:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-describe-#8216today%238217/</guid>
      <description>Today&amp;#8217;s task seems slightly more daunting than yesterday. Somehow I am supposed to describe my day in only one sentence. Shouldn&amp;#8217;t be too hard&amp;#8230;right? Author Liz Danzico.
 &amp;#8220;Your genuine action will explain itself, and will explain your other genuine actions. Your conformity explains nothing. The force of character is cumulative. – Ralph Waldo Emerson, Self-Reliance&amp;#8221;
 My Response: Don&amp;#8217;t let today get in the way of the rest of your life; you&amp;#8217;ll have struggles but keep your friends and family close, they&amp;#8217;re the best support you&amp;#8217;ll ever need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are You Happy?</title>
      <link>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/09/are-you-happy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2010 10:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/09/are-you-happy/</guid>
      <description>Author: Randy Clark
Recently, over lunch, Greg asked if I would guest post about separating work and Life. As I considered what I would like to share, I realized how many different approaches were available on this subject. Do I talk of social media and how difficult it is to separate work from social media 24&amp;frasl;7? How about strategies to balance your life? How to make work fun or eliminate stress?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>