<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>swimming on Greg McMullen</title>
    <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/swimming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in swimming on Greg McMullen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 11:00:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/swimming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2013-2014 Season Recap</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2014/05/2013-2014-season-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2014/05/2013-2014-season-recap/</guid>
      <description>The 2013-2014 season at Rose-Hulman ended better than I ever could have imagined. After breaking more than 20 records in the 2012-2013 season, I never would have imagined breaking another 13. We sent two to the NCAA Division III National Championships.
Both swam well and earned All-American status by finishing in the top 8.
Personal Challenges This season was easier than last year.
From my point of view, I had a very successful season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos: IWU vs Rose-Hulman</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2013/12/photos-iwu-vs-rose-hulman/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2013 14:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2013/12/photos-iwu-vs-rose-hulman/</guid>
      <description>Meet photos from the Illinois Wesleyan vs Rose-Hulman Institute of Technology swim meet on November 2, 2013.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Season Recap: 2012-13</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2013/05/season-recap-2012-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 12:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2013/05/season-recap-2012-13/</guid>
      <description>With my first collegiate season under my belt, I am definitely looking forward to my second year (and more, if possible).
We wrapped up the season with 20 individual records (more with diving) and had two compete at the NCAA Division III National Championships.
Challenges Being a first-year (first-time collegiate) coach was intimidating. While I felt the need to approach the athletes different, I didn&amp;#8217;t. They were responsive to my critiques and criticisms, inviting the views from a coach they didn&amp;#8217;t know that well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coaches and Our Health</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/05/coaches-and-our-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2012 22:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/05/coaches-and-our-health/</guid>
      <description>The other day, I finally decided to weigh myself. I weighed in at 194.4lbs. New goal, weigh in the 180&amp;#8217;s before August 11.
The immediate question on my mind is not, &amp;#8220;why don&amp;#8217;t I take better care of myself.&amp;#8221; Rather it&amp;#8217;s &amp;#8220;why is it coaches seem to take better care of their athletes than themselves.&amp;#8221; Maybe I&amp;#8217;m wrong, but I would love for others to chime in.
So I want to reach out to all gathering ideas on the subject and how we can change our actions to better portray the things we teach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bringing a Team Together</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/11/bringing-a-team-together/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 16:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/11/bringing-a-team-together/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m sitting on the bus on our way to Lawrence Central (and due to recent events the coaching staff needs to stagger their seating). I&amp;#8217;m in the back of the bus with all the &amp;#8220;close&amp;#8221; swimmers you can really see the camaraderie between the team.
At the same time you can also feel the sense of disconnect between swimmers of different backgrounds. Both of our team captains are sitting in the back minding themselves while the younger and less experienced swimmers sit quietly on their own.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>