<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coaching on Greg McMullen</title>
    <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/coaching/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coaching on Greg McMullen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 May 2012 22:22:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/coaching/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Coaches and Our Health</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/05/coaches-and-our-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2012 22:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/05/coaches-and-our-health/</guid>
      <description>The other day, I finally decided to weigh myself. I weighed in at 194.4lbs. New goal, weigh in the 180&amp;#8217;s before August 11.
The immediate question on my mind is not, &amp;#8220;why don&amp;#8217;t I take better care of myself.&amp;#8221; Rather it&amp;#8217;s &amp;#8220;why is it coaches seem to take better care of their athletes than themselves.&amp;#8221; Maybe I&amp;#8217;m wrong, but I would love for others to chime in.
So I want to reach out to all gathering ideas on the subject and how we can change our actions to better portray the things we teach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Risks; Meeting Opportunity</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/taking-risks-meeting-opportunity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2011 21:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/taking-risks-meeting-opportunity/</guid>
      <description>Recently I was talking to an online acquaintance regarding the process of making tough decisions. My question to you is why are you afraid to take the risks that will make you happy?
People are Safe You know what will make you happy don&amp;#8217;t you? So why aren&amp;#8217;t you doing everything you can to do it? I&amp;#8217;ve seen in my life that I need encouragement do try something different. When I saw the coaching position open I was hesitant to apply, why?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Law of the Lid</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/law-of-the-lid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 12:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/law-of-the-lid/</guid>
      <description>Recently I was given a copy of The 21 Irrefutable Laws of Leadership and decided that I will partake in applying these laws to my life online.
My hope is that I can also urge you, my readers and friends, to also partake and keep me accountable for my goals, dreams and ambitions as I also help you.
Major Goals List your major goals. No more than ten; no less than five.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Handle Disappointment?</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/07/do-you-handle-disappointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 11:53:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/07/do-you-handle-disappointment/</guid>
      <description>Success is Peace of Mind which is a direct result of self satisfaction in knowing you made the effort to do the best of which you are capable. - John Wooden
 If you were one of the many Americans watching the Women&amp;#8217;s National team make a run toward the FIFA Women&amp;#8217;s World Cup Final were you disappointed?
By looking at the team accomplishments, you&amp;#8217;ll proud!
Team USA Accomplishments  Hope Solo went 1,054 minutes without allowing a goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Makes you Better?</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/07/what-makes-you-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2011 13:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/07/what-makes-you-better/</guid>
      <description>I was recently interviewed for a head coach job at a swim club. I surprised myself when I was asked the question.
 What makes you different/better than the next person that we bring in?
 My response, &amp;#8220;Nothing.&amp;#8221;
What the @#$^% are you thinking? How am I supposed to know what makes me different from people I&amp;#8217;ve never met? For all I know they could be 30 years old and have coached for 15 years, am I better than them?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Courage to Connect</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-courage-to-connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2011 13:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-courage-to-connect/</guid>
      <description>Men imagine that they communicate their virtue or vice only by overt actions, and do not see that virtue or vice emit a breath every moment. &amp;#8211; Ralph Waldo Emerson
 Who is one person that you’ve been dying to connect with, but just haven’t had the courage to reach out to? First, reflect on why you want to get in touch with them. Then, reach out and set up a meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Come Alive!</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-come-alive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2011 00:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-come-alive/</guid>
      <description>Life wastes itself while we are preparing to live. – Ralph Waldo Emerson
 If you had one week left to live, would you still be doing what you’re doing now? In what areas of your life are you preparing to live? Take them off your To Do list and add them to a To Stop list. Resolve to only do what makes you come alive.
Bonus: How can your goals improve the present and not keep you in a perpetual “always something better” spiral?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sports and Education</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/01/sports-and-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 11:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/01/sports-and-education/</guid>
      <description>Now, to start things off I&amp;#8217;m a little upset and frustrated at this quote from Cam Newton after the Auburn Tigers beat the Oregon Ducks in the BCS Title game. So if this seems a little off topic, I want to apologize.
 &amp;#8220;I don&amp;#8217;t want nobody to feel sorry for me, because throughout this year didn&amp;#8217;t nobody feel sorry for Auburn,&amp;#8221; Newton said, setting a BCS record for double negatives in a single sentence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bringing a Team Together</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/11/bringing-a-team-together/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2010 16:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/11/bringing-a-team-together/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m sitting on the bus on our way to Lawrence Central (and due to recent events the coaching staff needs to stagger their seating). I&amp;#8217;m in the back of the bus with all the &amp;#8220;close&amp;#8221; swimmers you can really see the camaraderie between the team.
At the same time you can also feel the sense of disconnect between swimmers of different backgrounds. Both of our team captains are sitting in the back minding themselves while the younger and less experienced swimmers sit quietly on their own.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>