<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>personal marketing on Greg McMullen</title>
    <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/personal-marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in personal marketing on Greg McMullen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 19:16:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/tags/personal-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: My Personal (un)Shared Belief</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-my-personal-unshared-belief/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 19:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-my-personal-unshared-belief/</guid>
      <description>It is easy in the world to live after the world’s opinion; it is easy in solitude to live after our own; but the great man is he who in the midst of the crowd keeps with perfect sweetness the independence of solitude. &amp;#8211; Ralph Waldo Emerson, Self-Reliance
 The world is powered by passionate people, powerful ideas, and fearless action. What’s one strong belief you possess that isn’t shared by your closest friends or family?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>trust30: Describe &amp;#8216;Today&amp;#8217;</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-describe-#8216today%238217/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 11:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/06/trust30-describe-#8216today%238217/</guid>
      <description>Today&amp;#8217;s task seems slightly more daunting than yesterday. Somehow I am supposed to describe my day in only one sentence. Shouldn&amp;#8217;t be too hard&amp;#8230;right? Author Liz Danzico.
 &amp;#8220;Your genuine action will explain itself, and will explain your other genuine actions. Your conformity explains nothing. The force of character is cumulative. – Ralph Waldo Emerson, Self-Reliance&amp;#8221;
 My Response: Don&amp;#8217;t let today get in the way of the rest of your life; you&amp;#8217;ll have struggles but keep your friends and family close, they&amp;#8217;re the best support you&amp;#8217;ll ever need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding your First Job</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/09/finding-your-first-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2010 15:46:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/09/finding-your-first-job/</guid>
      <description>I know that when I started looking for jobs in college I looked for just about any place that was offering a job. The worst part about it was looking for something within my Degree (BSBA in Business Management). Obviously trying to find a &amp;#8220;management&amp;#8221; job was out of the question unless it would be lower-level.
Target your Ideal Job The best advice that I can even begin to give to Juniors and Seniors looking for a permanent job is to target the type of job that you want not just what you pre-qualify yourself for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Importance of your Avatar</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/08/importance-of-your-avatar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 10:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2010/08/importance-of-your-avatar/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;#8217;m sure that you&amp;#8217;ve heard the old phrase &amp;#8220;Don&amp;#8217;t Judge a book by it&amp;#8217;s cover&amp;#8221; but is that really how we operate? I know that I am guilty of judging someone based on their looks.
When we are looking for something or someone we look at links, videos, and images. What I want to talk about is your personal appearance, particularly in your online avatar. If you were to show up to an interview in a pair of ripped jeans, a dirty polo and basketball shoes would you be received the same as if you were to show up wearing a professionally cleaned and tailored suit?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>