<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coaching on Greg McMullen</title>
    <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/categories/coaching/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coaching on Greg McMullen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 11:00:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/categories/coaching/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2013-2014 Season Recap</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2014/05/2013-2014-season-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2014/05/2013-2014-season-recap/</guid>
      <description>The 2013-2014 season at Rose-Hulman ended better than I ever could have imagined. After breaking more than 20 records in the 2012-2013 season, I never would have imagined breaking another 13. We sent two to the NCAA Division III National Championships.
Both swam well and earned All-American status by finishing in the top 8.
Personal Challenges This season was easier than last year.
From my point of view, I had a very successful season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Farewell Letter</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2014/03/a-farewell-letter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 09:24:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2014/03/a-farewell-letter/</guid>
      <description>As many of you know, my time at Rose-Hulman was always limited. Sarah and I knew that match day would come and we would inevitably be told where we were going to live, not by our hearts, but by a computer system.
On Friday, March 21 we opened a letter, read the words and to saw we will be starting a new life in Northern Kentucky.
When I started coaching, I never envisioned leaving a program would be as hard as it is today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reaching Your Full Potential</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2013/08/reaching-your-full-potential/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2013 09:15:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2013/08/reaching-your-full-potential/</guid>
      <description>People look towards family and close friends for support. How often do these requests get laughed at? Ignored? Supported? Or encouraged? No matter the outcome, these situations strengthen connections and can often help when reaching your full potential.
Find what you love.
I&amp;#8217;ve come up with some fairly off-the-wall ideas from paintball, laser tag to a web design/development firm. All of them have come crashing down with love and support of our families.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Season Recap: 2012-13</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2013/05/season-recap-2012-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2013 12:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2013/05/season-recap-2012-13/</guid>
      <description>With my first collegiate season under my belt, I am definitely looking forward to my second year (and more, if possible).
We wrapped up the season with 20 individual records (more with diving) and had two compete at the NCAA Division III National Championships.
Challenges Being a first-year (first-time collegiate) coach was intimidating. While I felt the need to approach the athletes different, I didn&amp;#8217;t. They were responsive to my critiques and criticisms, inviting the views from a coach they didn&amp;#8217;t know that well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reaffirming a Coaching Career Choice</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2013/01/reaffirming-a-coaching-career-choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 09:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2013/01/reaffirming-a-coaching-career-choice/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I received a series of text messages from a former swimmer. I only coached this athlete for two high school seasons and not only did he have an impact on my life, but these messages clearly showed that I had an impact on his as well.
 Hey Coach Greg! I just wanted to shoot you a quick text here. I just wanted to let you know how grateful I was to have had you as my head coach senior year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coaches and Our Health</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/05/coaches-and-our-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2012 22:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/05/coaches-and-our-health/</guid>
      <description>The other day, I finally decided to weigh myself. I weighed in at 194.4lbs. New goal, weigh in the 180&amp;#8217;s before August 11.
The immediate question on my mind is not, &amp;#8220;why don&amp;#8217;t I take better care of myself.&amp;#8221; Rather it&amp;#8217;s &amp;#8220;why is it coaches seem to take better care of their athletes than themselves.&amp;#8221; Maybe I&amp;#8217;m wrong, but I would love for others to chime in.
So I want to reach out to all gathering ideas on the subject and how we can change our actions to better portray the things we teach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2011-2012 Season Recap</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/03/2011-2012-season-recap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 09:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2012/03/2011-2012-season-recap/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;#8217;s simple, Coaches and athletes have to have goals. However, you have to make sure that the athletes and coaching staff buy into those goals and are all on the same page too. How do you do that? How does it work? What does it look like before/during/after? Well, this season was all about that.
This season was a different monster; it was something I wasn&amp;#8217;t quite ready for. I was responsible for practice development, discipline and general team maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Law of the Lid</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/law-of-the-lid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2011 12:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/law-of-the-lid/</guid>
      <description>Recently I was given a copy of The 21 Irrefutable Laws of Leadership and decided that I will partake in applying these laws to my life online.
My hope is that I can also urge you, my readers and friends, to also partake and keep me accountable for my goals, dreams and ambitions as I also help you.
Major Goals List your major goals. No more than ten; no less than five.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Workout Ideas</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/simple-workout-ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 08:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/08/simple-workout-ideas/</guid>
      <description>Everyone&amp;#8217;s busy. How do you manage to get a workout in? Do you have an expensive gym membership? Do you just walk or run around your neighborhood? Or do you have trouble finding the motivation to do a workout?
Today, I&amp;#8217;m going to give you just a few simple workout ideas using nothing but a resistance band, AKA Stretch Cords.
Resistance bands come in different lengths and resistance levels. The nice thing about using resistance bands is that you don&amp;#8217;t have to worry about dropping something heavy on your foot, so this makes for a nice workout even when you are alone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Determining your Motivation Style</title>
      <link>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/07/determining-your-motivation-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 08:54:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gregoryamcmullen.com/posts/2011/07/determining-your-motivation-style/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;#8217;ve ever watched a college basketball game, the coaching staff in the locker room is trying to &amp;#8220;psych&amp;#8221; up the team. Sometimes it works; however, it also creates undue stress in what could be your top performers.
Motivation isn&amp;#8217;t taught. It&amp;#8217;s also something that a coach or parent isn&amp;#8217;t in control of. Allowing an athlete the ability to stay relaxed in a familiar environment is more motivating than anything a coach or parent can say.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>